shareme.com 2015-12-08

# Our Privacy Policy - Shareme.com respects your right to privacy

---|---  
| 

  * Business & Productivity Tools
  * Communications
  * Desktop Enhancements
  * Drivers
  * Educational
  * Games
  * Home & Personal
  * Internet
  * Mobile
  * Multimedia & Design
  * Network Tools
  * Programming
  * Security
  * Utilities
  * Web Authoring

####  Top Downloads

  * Visual Fractal 1.6

With this interesting fractal software, you can...

  * BootRacer 4.6.1.360

BootRacer Tests How Fast is your PC! It...

  * WinSesame 10.3

The most powerful encryption software to...

  * Crave Accounting Pro 1.7.5

Crave Accounting software is an easy to use...

  * Money Manager Ex 0.9.9.0

Money Manager Ex is a free, open-source,...

  * AgileTrack 0.7c 1.0

AgileTrack is an agile/extreme programming (XP)...

  * Wise PC 1stAid 1.31

An intelligent freeware to fix common PC...

####  New Downloads

  * StarCode Express Plus Point of Sale 23.0.0

StarCode Express is Single Terminal Point of...

  * dbForge Data Generator for SQL Server 3.7

dbForge Data Generator for SQL Server is a GUI...

  * dbForge Data Compare for SQL Server 4.0

dbForge Data Compare for SQL Server is a tool...

  * Database Workbench Pro 5.1.8

Cross database engine developer IDE for...

  * MicroOLAP Database Designer for MySQL 2.1.6

Visual development system intended for database...

  * Icecream PDF Split & Merge 3.0

Icecream PDF Split & Merge is a versatile...

  * MOBILedit 8.1

MOBILedit is the universal phone management...

  * Typograf font manager 5.2.1

Typograf is an easy to use Windows font...

  * Image for Windows with IFD GUI 2.98

Image for Windows is an affordable and reliable...

  * Duplicate Video Remover Free 1.4

Duplicate Video Remover Free - small but very...

####  Recent Searches

Opera Mini Handler S60 3rd, Mp4 Player Repair Tool Energy Sistem 3020, Free Autocad Stage Lighting SymbolsSend, Scratch On Pc Like, Activation Code For Regclean Pro, Data Recovery Sotware, Flash Softw, Motorola W385 Handset Adobe Flash Player, Stamp Download, Songs Of Ipl Teams Download, Active Desktop Recovery Software, Dwg Martin House, Start Up Activation Codes Straight Talk, Draw To Life, Us Air Force Museum Dayton Oh

#### Latest Reviews

  * Duplicate Image Remover Free    (Almon)

I have a lot of duplicate / similar images in my PC which I wanted to get rid of so I installed this program but sadly... 

  * PDF Viewer for Windows    (Marta)

How am I suppose to go up/ down faster becasue I didn't find any scrollbar. I can move only one page at a time. 

  * Kernel for PST Split    (Karras)

Very effective tool that repairs pst files flawlessly. I recommend everybody to use trail version for result and using... 

  * Exchange Email Repair    (Austin Williams)

I was very disappointed when my EDB mailbox had become inaccessible. Many thanks to this program which has recovered all... 

  * Marimo Dungeon    (James)

Very addicting game! You should get it. Only bad thing is you have to delete and download when u don't want a certain... 

  * Kernel for EML to PST    (Mike)

I tried different types of programs and this one was way better. I was able to convert without any error. 

  * Free Ovulation Calendar    (Garcia)

Best app of it's kind. Been using it for a long time and I am very happy with it. I always get accurate information and... 

  * How Repair Outlook PST    (Michael )

It is great tool to repair corrupt pst files. You can utilize this product to take care of issue like that. 

  * ShutUp10    (Adam)

It's easy to use and has done a great job for my windows 10 computer. Keep up the good work. 

  * Latest OST to PST    (Tom)

Fantastic software, it works very fast, easy to understand too. Converted ost file into pst in seconds, also recovered ost... 

| 

**Our Privacy Policy**

Shareme.com respects your right to privacy.

**What information do we collect?  
**Some technical information is collected automatically on each page in order to give us an idea of how people are finding our website, what technologies they are using to access it and which pages interest them. Each time a visitor loads a page from a website is counted as one 'page load'. About once a month we also collect the current set of page load information to look for trends, for example changes in the screen resolution, operating system or browser that is most often used. We take this information into account when planning for usability and accessibility in website design. We also collect information on how visitors reach our website, including search engine use, search key word use, and links referring visitors to our website. We use this information in our search engine optimisation and marketing strategies. Some examples of the information we collect and analyse include: the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your browser type and version, your operating system and screen resolution. We do not collect personally identifiable information about our visitors without their consent.  If you join a mailing list operated by us, you will be able to unsubscribe at any time. 

**Third-Party Advertisers**  
Our site includes third-party advertising and links to other websites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party websites. Our advertisers will generally store cookies on visitor's computers to record information including which advertisement they followed to reach the advertiser's website, and the date when they visited. Depending on the advertiser, cookies will expire (ie be automatically deleted) after different lengths of time.   
We use Google Adsense to support our site. Ads provided by Google AdSense, are targeted to be relevant to the content of the website and / or page they are on (ie they get the information from the website contents not the visitors themselves). Google Adsense uses cookies and web beacons to target and measure effectiveness of ads they serve on user pc. Here you can find [Google's Privacy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html) information.

**Software Listing**  
All the software programs published by shareme.com are provided by the third party software producers. Any questions complaints or claims related to the software should be directed to the appropriate Author or Company responsible for developing the software. All other trademarks are the sole property of their respective owners. The files and programs made available are indexed from servers all over the world. If you found any software is in violation of any copyright or trademark, let us know and we will delete its listing from shareme.com site.

**Disclaimer**  
The files and programs made available are indexed from servers all over the world. Each user is responsible to virus check any program downloaded from the site before installation. shareme.com is not responsible for any loss or damage resulting from users' downloading or use of any such programs or files.

**Links to Other Websites**  
This site contains links to other sites. shareme.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of other web sites before disclosing any personal information on another site. These other sites may independently collect data, solicit personal information, or send their own cookies to you. The Company is not responsible for any use of the information including click-stream data that you may create when using such third party web sites. You should carefully review the privacy policies of these third party web sites in order to determine how they treat your personal information. 

**Contact us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, you can contact us

---|---  
  
Welcome to the ShareMe. Shareme is a dedicated internet portal bringing users the latest shareware & freeware from the world's best Software Authors. Shareme allows Shareware & Freeware Authors to submit their latest wares, so you the user are able to download their latest software updates all the time, after they are released! Always visit Shareme for your software needs.
